audiosparx.com 2012-09-22

# AudioSparx Privacy Policy

sound effects on itunes,  
audio clips sound effects,  
special effect sounds,  
free sound fx ringtones,  
thunder and rain sound effects,  
free sound effects gulls,  
dun dun dun sound clip,  
sound of throwing horse shoes,  
buy sound effects for making videos,  
free bruce lee sound effects,  
thunder sound effects,  
motorbike sound effects,  
power point sound effects people,  
hammer sound effects,  
gear animation sounds,  
sound effects flicker on,  
planet exploding sound effect,  
fx,  
royal fam theme music sound fx,  
audio wav files 

| 

**Privacy Policy of AudioSparx  **

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.**

** 1.  What Personal Information Do We Collect and Save?**

  * **Information You Provide.**  We receive and store information you enter.  For example, when you search for or buy a product, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card.  You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features.  We collect and save the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you.    
 
  * **Cookies.** Like many websites, we use "cookies".  Your browser will automatically store one cookie that allows us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience.  And most importantly, the cookie is what maintains your "logged in" state once you register and login to the site.  If you delete our cookie from your browser, you will no longer be logged into our web site.

**Other Information:** Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address.  IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted.  In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site. 

** 2.  How Do We Use Your Information?**

  * **Customized Shopping.   **We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience. We operate multiple different web sites which all share a common database, hence information you enter on one web site will be available for your immediate use on the other web sites as applicable.  This includes client login account information, credit card information, shipping information and various other relevant information.    
 
  * **Composers and Publishers.   **When you purchase a music track here for commercial use, for each track you purchase you must submit a track usage report indicating how each track will be used.  The information you submit with each track report will be shared with the composer(s) and publisher(s) of each track to inform them about how their music is being used and who is using it.  The person or organization that is administering publishing for music tracks may contact you directly to request information about your use of the music in order to be able to file a cue sheet.  Don't be alarmed, filing cue sheets for broadcast or other public uses of music tracks is a normal part of this business.   
 
  * **Agents.** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to only your personal information as needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.   
 
  * **Special Offers**.  We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to opt-out of receiving such offers.  Please see the opt-in/opt-out selection at the end of this policy.    
 
  * **Business Development and Transfers**. As we continue to develop our business, we develop new web sites internally and we might sell or buy other companies or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we are acquired, your customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the new owner.  
 
  * **Law Enforcement.    **If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law.  We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.   
 
  * **Internal Reference.**   The information we collect and save is used for internal reference purposes, to administer our business operations in a proper manner.  We do not delete your information, and you can not request to have it deleted from our system.  We retain it forever for internal reference purposes, in case we need to research a transaction or some other activity on our web site.

** 3.  How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.   
 
  * We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list, including one-way encryption of your password.   
 
  * We use encryption to protect your credit card information.  
 
  * We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion.   
 
  * We limit access to your information on a need to know basis.   
 
  * We only transmit the your credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing or as otherwise necessary.   
 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.   
 
  * No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security.  However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure. 

**4.   Your Choice:  Opt-in or Opt-out.**

> It is your choice whether to receive emails or special offers from us about sales promotions and new music libraries that are added to our site.  
>  By default, newly registered clients are opted-in.  During registration, to not receive the emails, please opt-out.

** 5.  Children**

>  We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

** 6.  Other Websites**

> Various Web sites may be linked to from this site.  If you click through to another web site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site.  We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy.  Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others.  You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance ([www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)).

** 7.  Contact Us**

> If you ever need assistance with the features, products or services offered on this web site, please contact us at [ info@audiosparx.com](mailto:info@audiosparx.com) and we will be happy to assist you. 

** 8.  Reserved Rights**

> We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future.

*************************************

| 

downloading audio sounds,  
sound effects music,  
soundclips,  
counter bell sound effect,  
howling wind sound effect free,  
free news sound effects download,  
media frenzy sound effects,  
game show sound effects,  
shot gun bangs sound effect,  
odometer sound fx,  
free sound effects of little girl crying,  
smoke and cough wav sounds,  
download robot sound effects,  
ship crashing sound effect,  
sound effect paint brush,  
free bees sound effect,  
free downloads sounds,  
video sound effects,  
portal wav files,  
sound effect browser
